India114，116，260到达指定位置
We have India 114, 116, and 260 in position.
104号在你前方500米，请指示
Flight 104 is 500 yards in trail, waiting for your go.
就是这里，他们就是我们要找的人
That's it, right there. There's our guy.
开始向目标靠近
Begin your final approach to the target.
104明白
Flight 104, copy that.
我操！
Shit!
沃尔特，快醒醒 海关警察来了
Walter, wake up. Customs.
什么？谁？
What? Who?
我们需要这个该死的包，他妈的钥匙在哪里？
We need the fucking bag. Where the fuck is the key?
绑紧绳子，然后去另一边警戒
Tighten that line. Now secure the other side.
他妈的慢点
Easy, easy up.
冷静，冷静
Okay, Okay.
搞快点，快点 把东西放进包里
Hurry up. Come on, put it in the bag.
快点！
Come on!
拉上去，快点 快点
Pull this up. Come on, come on. Let's go!
快走，安迪
Go, Andy.
站住！联邦警察！不要动！
Stop! Federal officer! Don't move!
抱歉打扰一下，你们能不能给我一分钟
Excuse me. Excuse me, y'all. Can I have everybody's attention?
我想快速的敬一杯给新郎和新娘，丹尼和谢丽
I want to do a quick toast to the bride and groom, Danny and Shelly.
恭喜你们！
Congratulations.
克里斯 我真不敢相信，我他妈竟然结婚了
I can't believe it, man. I'm fucking married, Chris.
丹尼，我了解的，我当时就在你身边
Danny, I know. I was standing right there with you.
你看，这个人是他妈的谁？
Look, what about this fucking guy?
他是我最好的朋友，在我婚礼上最好的人
He's my best friend, best man at my wedding.
他竟然不记得这就是我举行婚礼的地方
He doesn't even remember that this is where my reception was.
谢谢老天，他还是清醒的
Thank God he's sober.
你不记得了吗？
You don't remember?
我只记得我扔了凯特的鞋子
I remember throwing up on Kate's shoes.
是的，我也记得
Yeah, I remember, too.
关于这件事，我很抱歉
I apologized for that.
大家跟我一起做
Everybody, do it like this.
我是说哈，你就像列农和麦卡特尼一样在走私
I mean, you were like the Lennon and McCartney of smuggling.
你他妈是怎样走私法拉利的？你把它藏在哪里的？
How do you smuggle a fucking Ferrari? Where do you hide it?
我们没有藏
We didn't.
我们让海关把它扣押在港口
We let customs seize it in port.
把你手机给我
Give me your phone.
你把车子里面的东西都拿出来
You take the guts out.
包括传输布线系统
The transmission, the wiring system.
把这些没用的东西都拿出来，放进其它箱子里
Take all that shit out, hide it inside other containers.
然后等到海关拍卖这部车的时候
So, when customs auctions off the car,
他得到的只是法拉利外壳，而没有其他设备
he gets himself a Ferrari for next to nothing.
他买了一只空壳？
He just bought the empty shell?
是的，他在拍卖会上买到的只是空壳
Yes, he got the empty shell at the auction.
所以我们
And then we...
卖给他其他的部分 车子里面的部分
Sell him the missing parts. ...sold him back the guts.
就这样他就买到了一辆新法拉利
And he's got himself a new Ferrari
而费用却不到买一辆垃圾本田
for less than you paid for that piece-of-shit Honda.
真是辆好本田（指赚的钱挺多）
It's a nice Honda.
是的，我就是靠这个生活的，还不错吧？
Yeah, that's why you live in it, right?
因为这是一辆很好的本田车
Because it's a nice fucking Honda.
我能和我老婆跳个舞吗？
Can I dance with my wife?
嗨，兄弟，玩得怎么样？
Hey, what's up, buddy?
如果你有的话，能再给我一瓶这个吗？
Can I get another one of these when you get a chance?
嗨，克里斯
Hey, Chris.
你好，牧师
Church, hey.
帅哥，最近过得怎么样？
How are you doing, man?
很久没见到你了，你都在哪里发财呀？
Long time, no see. Where you been?
嗯，我现在住在阿尔及尔（阿尔及利亚首都）
Well, I'm living out in Algiers now.
你他妈去哪里做什么？
The fuck are you doing out there?
那里很不错，我喜欢那里
It's nice, I like it out there.
很适合家庭居住
It's good for the family.
克里斯，像你这样的男人是不属于阿尔及尔的
A guy like you don't belong in Algiers, Chris.
你现在在哪里打工？
What are you doing for work?
我开始自己创业，做报警系统的
I started my own business, setting up alarm systems.
帮我加满，好吗？
Fill that up, will you?
你的老朋友蹲监狱去了把你吓着了吗？
Your old man getting jailed freak you out? Huh?
我觉得差不多吧
I guess.
再加上我又有个老婆和两个小儿子，你懂吧
That, and having a wife and two little boys, you know?
我懂
Yeah.
克里斯，虽然如此，但是你还是得做回你的老本行
You've got to stick to what you're good at, though, Chris.
听着，我为了你老汉，花钱雇人保护那个船长
Listen, I offered to take care of that ship captain for your dad.
他却说不要我这么做
He said no.
不管怎么样，克里斯，如果你想好了要回来
Anyway, Chris, if you're ever thinking of getting back in,
告诉我，好吗？
let me know, okay?
好吗？
Yeah?
- 好  - 那就好
- Yeah.     - Good.
我都不知道为什么我们要第一个干这件事
I don't even know why we're doing this in the first place.
你就相信我吧，好吗？很简单的
Just trust me, okay? It will be cool.
如果我们想要逃跑，这样事情只会很糟
If we try to run, it will make it worse.
他们人呢？
Where are these guys?
他们来了，他们来了
Here we go, here we go.
现在开始要冷静
Be cool, now.
开始了，开始了
Here we go, here we go.
你好，兄弟
Hey, man.
海关发现了我们，我们只好把东西扔了
Customs boarded us, we had to dump the package.
你真扔了？
You did?
我们也是么得法子啊
We had no choice.
是吧？
Right?
我们真的是没有办法啊，大哥
Nothing we could do, man.
就是这样
That's it.
我怎么给你说的？我说过这事很简单的
What did I say? I told you it was cool.
算了吧，大哥，我们走吧
Come on, man, let's get the fuck out of here.
你好？
Hello?
是我弟弟
It's my brother.
怎么了？他还好吧？
What happened? Is he okay?
不好，我们现在得过去
No. We've got to go now.
啥子啊？
What?
沃尔特正在做手术
Walter is in surgery.
安迪，到底他妈的发生什么事情了？
What the fuck happened, Andy?
出了一点意外
It was an accident.
你听到起，你太不会骗人了 所以不要想着骗我
You know what? You're a shitty liar, so don't even fucking try.
我跟你说话的时候你要看着我
Look at me when I'm talking to you.
我当时在运货
I was running something.
我们被发现了，所以我把东西扔了
We got boarded, and I dumped it.
你把什么扔了？
You dumped what?
毒品
The coke.
我草！
Oh, fuck.
足足有10多磅
It was over 10 pounds.
给谁的？
For who?
给蒂姆·布里格斯
For Tim Briggs
还有这些
and those guys.
准备杀死了我的人
They're going to kill me.
安迪，他们不会杀你的
Andy, they're not going to kill you.
乱七八糟的事真多
It was a lot of stuff.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你是该他妈感到抱歉
You should be fucking sorry.
他还好吗？
Is he all right?
不，他的小逼脑袋不知道在想些什么
No, the little fuck head was running something
他把东西扔了，现在他欠人家了
and he dumped it. Now he owes.
哪个？他欠哪个的？
Who? Who does he owe?
蒂姆·布里格斯
Tim Briggs.
你去问问，看能不能找到点线索，好吗？
Ask around, see what you can find out, all right?
凯特怎么样？
How is Kate?
不怎么好
Not good.
我真不敢相信他这样做了
I can't believe he did that.
我退出的时候，我就给他说过不要跟这些人打交道
When I quit, I told him to stay away from these guys.
拜托，如果你有什么办法解决这件事，现在就告诉我
Please, if you had anything to do with this, just tell me right now.
我不是才告诉你吗
I just told you.
好吧
Okay.
他是我兄弟
He's my little brother.
我知道，我会处理这件事的
I know. I'm going to take care of it.
我抱住你了
I got you.
我明早打给你
I'll call you in the morning.
好，要得
Okay, no problem.
晚安
Good night.
你说是“安保王公司”安装的系统
So you said King Security put the system in?
是的，这东西帮了我不少忙
That's right. A lot of good it did.
这是一个不错的系统，但是你的锁就是个笑话
It's a decent system, but your locks are a joke.
只要知道反应时间的人
Anybody who knows the response time
都可以自如的进出
is going to be able to get in and out.
给我一分钟时间好吗，先生？
Can you excuse me for one second, sir?
好的
Yes.
是关于布里格斯的，凯尔的哥哥
It's about Briggs, Kyle's brother.
然后呢？
Yeah, and?
我也不知道，你等一下
I don't know, hold on.
各位！各位！今天情况怎么样？
Guys! Guys! How are we doing today?
上周是不是一直在开工？
Is my office still going to be done last week?
早上不错吧？
You having a nice morning?
很好
Good!
布里格斯两个月前出狱了
Briggs got out of prison two months ago.
他经常去"老点"酒吧
He hangs out at the Old Point Bar.
等我忙完了手上的工作我会去那里看能不能跟他谈谈
I'll pop over there after I'm done work and see if I can talk to him.
不好意思，先生
Sorry about that, sir.
这些摄像头很小很好
The cameras are nice and small,
刚好合适安装在上面的角落里
they'll fit right up there in the corner.
我操！
Oh, shit!
克里斯·法拉迪，死而复生，兄弟！
Chris Farra-day, back from the dead, man!
很高兴见到你，兄弟
Good to see you, man.
我操 这哥们在这里可是世界级的走私犯
Oh, shit. This man was a world-class smuggler here.
你曾是他妈的胡迪尼（著名的魔术师），哥们
You were fucking Houdini, man.
他曾经跟我哥混，愿上帝安息他可悲的灵魂
Yeah, he used to run with my brother, God rest his miserable soul.
真可惜你对你那屎脑壳舅子的责任感
Too bad your skill didn't rub off
没有消失
on your shithead brother-in-law.
是的，我晓得，他是个傻逼
No, I know, he's a fuck-up.
但是他是我老婆的弟弟
But he's my wife's little brother.
我只是希望你能理解这样的家庭因素
I was hoping you understand it's family,
也许我们可以想出解决的办法
maybe we could work something out.
好吧，我不知道 你想怎样解决？
Well, I don't know. What do you want to work out?
你想跟我解决这件事？
You want to work out something with me?
我会想法子还给你那些货的钱
I can figure out a way to pay you back the buy money.
不，对于我来说那批货值70万美元
No, that's worth 700 grand to me.
- 少来了，哥们  - 不，你少来，哥们
- Oh, come on, man. - No, come on, man.
你准备要我为这次损失的货物负全责？
You're going to try to charge me full freight for a bad run?
海关检查，扔掉货物，你知道游戏规则的
Customs boards the boat, you dump that shit. You know how it goes.
你知道你哥哥在的时候我放你哥多少次水吗？
You know how many passes I gave your brother in his day?
是啊，不过我恨我哥
Yeah, I hated my brother.
那你想怎样嘛，你想慢慢筹款？
What do you want to do, a payment plan?
对你来说，我不会像是个银行吧？
What, do I look like a bank to you?
不是，我只是希望你他妈在这件事里能负起你的责任
No, I was just hoping you could be fucking reasonable, here.
这里已经没有你说话的份了，兄弟！
This ain't your world any more, man!
你现在只是个旁观者，你不能利用你没有的地位
You're a tourist, you can't trade on status you don't have.
我还有很多账单要付
I got bills to pay.
你知道的，谁把事情搞砸了，就是谁的问题
You know, when people fuck that up, that's their fucking problem.
你觉得这很好笑？你有没有账单要付？
You think that's funny? You got bills?
我喜欢你的衣服
I like your outfit.
我喜欢你哥哥
I liked your brother.
我们今天来到了这里，这是一件很重要的事情
We're here today, that's the important thing.
所以你知道的，学会释然和遵从上帝的旨意
So, you know, learning to let go and let God
是帮我渡过这些事情的力量
is what's been pulling me through all of this.
在我杀死布里格斯前，你得劝阻我
You're going to have to talk me down before I fucking kill Briggs.
可能会更好的
Probably be better off.
我曾经也是一名酗酒者
I'm one drink away from the worst day of my life.
我该怎么办？
What should I do?
坐在这个圈子里的人都有过这样的想法吧？
...sitting in this circle that's had that same thought, right?
你最需要做的其实是，继续前进
That's all you gotta do is work the steps.
我不会再去运货了
I'm not doing another run.
他妈的想都别想
No fucking way.
我或许可以弄到买货的那笔钱，应该没有问题
I could probably get us the buy money, no problem.
不，我最后还是有些其他想法
No, I finally got something going.
我要找机会做好这件事情
I'm not going to chance fucking it up.
克里斯你这么做不好的
It's not going away, Chris.
哪个想跟我们分享一下他的故事吗？
Does somebody want to share?
塞巴斯蒂安，想分享点你的故事给大家吗？
Sebastian? Want to share a little bit with us?
- 好的 - 噢，好吧
- Okay.     - Oh, yeah.
去做你自己的事情吧
Go do your thing.
想出去走走吗？
You don't want to stick around?
不了，听他们说故事让我很有感觉
No, I get far too emotional hearing that story.
- 哈啰，大家好 我是塞巴斯蒂安  - 你过得怎么样？塞巴斯蒂安
- Hey, everyone, I'm Sebastian. - How are you doing, Sebastian?
怎么了？
What the hell happened?
沃尔特昨晚挂了
Walter died last night.
布里格斯昨天来医院了
Briggs came to the hospital.
他说这都是我的错
He said it was all on me.
克里斯，我一直在打电话
I keep getting calls, Chris,
他们妈的一直在对我说怎么弄我
and they're talking about how they're going to fucking torture me.
我要跑路了，一段时间内我是不回来了
I'm shipping out in the next couple of days. I'm not coming back.
帮我个忙，在我离开之前不要告诉凯特
Do me a favor, and don't tell Kate. Not until I'm gone.
在我退出走私的时候
When I stopped doing runs,
你答应我不再做走私这些破事的
you promised me you were gonna stay out of this shit.
老哥，你想让我说什么？
What do you want me to say, man?
什么他妈也不要说了
Not a fucking word!
我以前都是单枪匹马，你现在却有顾虑
I didn't have anybody to tell me I was fucking up. You do!
你把你姐姐跟孩子些都牵扯进来了你他妈晓得不？
And you put your sister and the boys in this shit?
你他妈屎老壳到底在想些什么？
What the fuck is wrong with you?
我草
Whoa.
你他妈不应该来我地盘的
You don't come to my fucking place.
我只是想来告诉你
I just came to tell you
欠你的钱过几个月再还
that I'm going to have your money within a month.
只要你不要去碰安迪
Just stay away from Andy.
我等不了那么久
I ain't waiting that long.
如果你敢碰他，老子就不还钱
Well, I ain't paying if he's dead.
如果他死球了，钱还没还
If a guy dies owing something
老子就找他的家人还
his family inherits the debt.
给你两周时间
So I'll give you two weeks.
如果到时不还钱，我会把你们都杀了
If not, I'm going to come after the both of you.
如果还是不行，那我就一直要债下去
Then, all the way down the line.
直到你的妻子，你儿子
I'll come asking your wife for it, your kids...
你他妈以为就你有这鸡巴破枪吗？
Do you think you're the only guy with a fucking gun?
老子会还你那点小钱的
You'll get your fucking money.
但是你他妈再敢提我老婆
But if you ever mention my wife
我孩子，老子爆了你菊花
and my kids again, you're done.
听清楚了吗？你他妈死定了
You hear me? You are fucking done!
爸爸
Daddy.
没事，宝贝 回屋里去
It's okay, sweetie. Go back inside.
没事，宝贝 你老爸只是跟我只是在玩呢，好吗？
It's okay, sweetie. Daddy and I were just playing, okay?
好吧 我们只是玩玩
It's okay. Yeah, we're just playing.
是啊，我和你只是玩玩
Yeah, me and Daddy were just fucking playing.
滚上去
Get up there.
噢耶，我们会再次玩的
Yeah, we'll play again.
你爸爸没事
Daddy is okay.
没关系的
It's all right.
你他娘的瞄什么瞄
What the fuck are you looking at?
你留在车里，我去跟她谈谈
You stay in the car, I'll go talk to her.
好吧
Okay.
- 你好，克里斯 - 你好
- Hey, Chris. - Hey, how are you?
嗨
Hi.
Hey.
你没事吧？
Everything okay?
嗯，我想跟你谈几分钟
Yeah, I just wanted to talk to you for a minute.
好吧
Okay.
我得和安迪上船去解决这件事情
I got to get on the ship with Andy and try to fix this.
你是在开玩笑吗？
Are you fucking kidding?
那我怎么办，让他自己去处理？
What am I going to do, let him go alone?
当然不是 我们想想其他的办法
No, we're going to think of something else.
没有其他办法了，好吗？
There's nothing else to do, okay?
我不得不告诉你
I hate to tell you,
你家那小逼东西已经把我们
but that little dumb fuck has put us
置于最危险的境地了，了解？
in the worst possible position, okay?
如果他们拿不到钱，他们就会来找我们
And if they don't get the money from him, they're coming after us.
你还想我怎么样嘛？
So what else do you want me to do?
我想你怎样？
You know what I don't want to do?
我想等你进笼子里了，我们像以前看你老汉一样去看你
I don't want to fucking visit you in jail like we're visiting your dad,
而且我自己养大我们的孩子
and raising those kids on my own.
这只是我
So it's my...
我不想跟你吵这些，好吗？
I don't want to fight with you about this, okay?
我知道我在干什么，好吗？
I know what I'm doing, all right?
你能相信我吗？
Will you just trust me?
求你了
Please?
不会有事的
Nothing is going to happen.
好吗？我向你保证
All right? I promise. Mmm.
那个混蛋布里格斯在这里呆过很多年了
That shit bag Briggs was here for a couple of years.
他曾经试图用煤渣砸了别人的脑壳
He tried to smash some guy's head in with a cinder block.
听着，我跟塞巴斯蒂安提过这些
Look, I mentioned this to Sebastian.
我们准备再运一次货
We're doing another run.
你能把我送上你的老船吗？
Can you get me on your old boat?
你是在说波登号？
You mean the Borden?
记得你小时候，你跟塞巴斯蒂安
Remember when you were little, you and Sebastian,
你们冲进麦克提尔的仓库
you broke into McTier's warehouse,
偷了狂欢节所有的珠宝
stole all that Mardi Gras jewelry,
你还拿个大盒子再次回到那个地方把所有的珠子都偷跑了
and you came back to the house with a great big box of them beads?
你以为那些都是钻石
You thought they were diamonds.
你一脸欢喜，像他妈中了六合彩一样
You were grinning like you just won the fucking lottery.
你还说
And you said,
“你不必再在船上工作了”
"You don't have to work on that boat no more."
我总是幻想着那一天
I always think about that.
我一生最值得骄傲的一天就是你退出这个行当
The proudest day of my life was when you turned legit,
并且开始了你自己的创业
and you started your own business, and you got out of the life.
我知道你也是身不由已
I know you got to do what you got to do.
我明白的
I got it.
家人就是家人
Family is family.
我会把你送上船的
I'll get you on the boat.
但是等你上去了以后
But you get in,
你得想好退路
you got to get back out.
我和安迪坐波登号去巴拿马
Me and Andy are shipping out to Panama with the Borden.
那老男人的船？
The old man's boat?
是的，他让我们上去了
Yeah, he got us on.
船长怎么办？
What about Captain Camp?
我知道，我知道 不要担心
I know. I know. Don't worry about it.
这是什么东西？
What's this?
什么？
What's what?
每次我来的时候，你都有些新玩意
Every time I come here, you got new shit.
我要把它放在一起，放在我准备好的地方
I'm getting it together, I'm getting the place ready.
这是一张"坏屁股"咖啡桌
It's a bad-ass coffee table.
不是放脚在上面
That is not for shoes.
看来我OUT了，我都忘记什么是"坏屁股"了
I must be out of touch. I don't know what's bad-ass any more
因为这看起来也只是个很便宜的"屁股"
because this looks cheap-ass.
你快成宅男了
You're turning into The Birdcage.
我是说
I mean...
那么我们在巴拿马认识谁？
So who do we know in Panama?
你准备去看看鲁本吗？
Are you going to go see Ruben?
哥们，不搞毒了
Dude, no drugs.
其他什么活还能有这么高的回报率？
What else has that kind of profit margin?
埃德温在巴拿马
Edwin is in Panama.
现在？
Currency?
我们要带回好鸡巴多吨才值我们的时间
We have to bring back a shit-ton to make it worth our while.
好吧，我们能拿多少拿多少
All right, so I'll bring back a shit-ton.
好吧，1千500万摆四堆，像这么大
Okay, 15 million on four stacks this big.
差不多一辆Mini的大小
It's like the size of a Mini Cooper.
你准备藏在哪里？
Where are you going to hide it?
看我的
That's my problem.
我需要波登号船员名单
I need the Borden's crew manifest.
噢，老天 你在开玩笑吧
Oh, God. You got to be kidding me.
噢，我喜欢塔里克·摩丁，他是一个可怕的厨师，但是在船上却还不错
Oh, I like Tarik Mortin. He's a horrible chef, but he's great on runs.
拉·克劳德是他妈的酒鬼
Le Cloud's a fucking drunk.
新婚的人？
Newlywed?
他不怎么样，但是我们认识很久了
He's not great on runs, but we've known him a long time.
奥拉夫非常结实，我们需要一个人在机房
Olaf's solid, we need somebody in the engine room.
好吧 虽然组不成天龙特工队，但是已经是最好的了
Well, it's no A-Team, but it's the best we can do.
开始吧，施展你的才华 去个电话，帮我搞到TWIC卡
Come on, work your magic. Make the call, get me a TWIC card.
你好，小盆友
Hi, sweet pea.
我要你帮我弄一张TWIC卡，名字为克里斯·法拉迪
I need you to push through a TWIC card for Chris Farraday.
我收到你的信息了 都过了3年你才给我打电话？
I got your message. It only took you three years to call me?
你又重操旧业了吗？
Are you back in business?
不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no.
我只是想要一些东西
I need something, though.
记得我们上一次跑船吗？那些搞笑的钱？
Remember our last run? The funny money?
在下周前我就要钱，但是可能会多很多
I need that exact same shit by next week, but a lot more.
四位差不多
Four times as much.
我们还需要一辆足够大的车运送，你看行吗？
And we need a van big enough to transport it, okay?
没问题 我会弄到的
Okay. I'll be here.
加油，米奇！
Come on, Mikey!
什么是搞笑的钱？
What's funny money?
啥？没什么 只是老爸工作上的一些事情
Huh? Nothing. That's just work stuff for Dad.
你曾被指控进行间谍活动吗？
Have you ever been convicted of espionage?
只要回答是或者不是，我们很快就好
Just answer yes or no, we'll get through this really quickly.
没有
No.
煽动叛乱，间谍，煽动叛乱，叛国？
Sedition, or conspiracy to commit espionage, sedition, treason?
一起吗？
Together?
我接到了你的航运申请
I received your shipping application, Mr...
拉科瓦斯基
Lakowski.
拉科瓦斯基先生
Mr. Lakowski.
拉科瓦斯基先生，我准备给你标准20米长的干货
Señor Lakowski, I'm getting you a 20-foot standard dry.
你希望我们帮你安装好吗？
Would you like us to load it?
不用了，我会找人处理 我只是想要那个箱子
No, I've got somebody to take care of that. I just need the container.
好吧，我们给你箱子
Okay, we'll leave the container
你在巴拿马港口等着就好了
standing by for you at the port of Panama.
你准备装运什么？
And what are you shipping?
一辆车
Avan.
给你
Here you go.
拿钱挣钱吧，宝贝
It takes money to make money, baby.
谢谢
Thank you.
别把船搞沉了，爸爸
Don't sink, Daddy.
没事的，孩子
Okay, buddy.
你会错过我的季后赛的
You're going to miss my playoff game.
我知道，我很抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
你妈妈会给我照很多你打球时的照片的，好吗？
Your mom is going to take lots of pictures for me, okay?
在我回来之前，你们自己做主
You guys are in charge till I get back.
我爱你们
I love you, guys.
早点回来吧，好吗？
Just come home, okay?
谢谢你做的一切，克里斯
Thank you for doing this, Chris.
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - Love you, too.
没事的
It's going to be okay.
请出示身份证，把手指放在扫描议上
ID, please. Finger on the scanner.
- 坎普船长 - 收锚
- Captain Camp. - Get the trunk.
把船长的地毯都收拾干净了
Get that Captain's carpet cleaner up to the bridge.
约翰，能帮我一下吗？
John, you want to give me a hand?
喂
Hey!
你是上铺，我睡下铺
You're up top. I get the bottom bunk.
真的，好吧
Yeah, no kidding.
别装着你很不喜欢干这件事情一样
Don't act like you don't like this shit.
为什么，很明显吗？
Why, is it that obvious?
我超爱的，但是不要告诉你姐姐哦
I love it, but don't tell your sister.
好了，走吧 你等下再睡你的美容觉 我们走
All right, come on. You can get your beauty rest later, let's go.
我的手，我的手
My arm, my arm.
小心
Keep an eye out.
喂，有人来了
Hey, someone's coming.
怎么了，克里斯？
What's up, Chris?
你好，克里斯
Hi, Chris.
克里斯
Chris.
快看这妈逼的
Look at this motherfucker.
奥拉夫 很高兴见到你
Olaf. Good to see you, man.
怎么样，塔里克？还好吧？
What's up, Tarik? You okay?
啥小啊
What's up, man?
- 你的伙伴都还好吧？都还好吧？ - 都好，都好
- How's your folks? Everybody's good? - Good, good.
那是一个很饿的人才吃得下的量
That's a hungry man's appetite.
真他妈好吃
This is real good.
怎么样？伙计
How you doing, buddy?
你他妈的在我船上干什么？
What the fuck are you doing on my ship?
你他妈有没有检查船员名单？
Did you even check the goddamn crew manifest?
你他妈的怎么让巴德·法拉迪的杂逼些都上了我的船？
How the fuck do you let Bud Farraday's spawn aboard my ship?
DHS把他去掉了的 他是最后加进名单的
DHS cleared him. He was added at the last minute.
好吧，现在我要给他降级
All right, I'm demoting him to ship's boy.
好的，船长
Yes, sir.
你去擦掉脏的地方，并滚出我的视野
You scrub dirt and stay the fuck out of my sight.
不然的话，我就把你丢海里去
Otherwise you might have an accident,
让你淹死
and wind up in the drink.
带他去拿地毯清洁机
Show him where the carpet cleaner is.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
噢，我草 地毯清洁机
Oh, man, carpet cleaner.
我们走，地毯博士
Let's go, Rug Doctor.
噢，你被提拔了吗？他们给你新的条纹在那
Oh, you got promoted? They gave you some new stripes on there.
我做我的清洁工，你还是船长的爆菊工具
I'll be ship's boy. You're still Captain's bitch boy.
是啊，是啊
Yeah, yeah.
好的
Okay.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
都他妈的喝高了，没有一个人在他妈的工作
Everybody's drinking tall boys, and nobody's fucking working.
所以呢？兄弟
What's up, man?
你准备把船长拉下水还是想怎么办？
Are you bringing the Captain in on this or what?
我草 当然不是
Fuck, no.
好吧，我记得在这里跟你的POPS说过同样的话
Well, I remember talking to your pops in this same room.
他的回答一样 我们知道是怎么一回事
He said that same shit. We know how that turned out.
你相信我不？
Do you trust me or not?
我相信啊，相信
I do. I do.
那么我们在运什么东西？
So what are we running?
航运托盘装载的5000张完整无缺的超级票据
A shipping pallet loaded up with 5,000 uncut sheets of super notes.
最好的假币才能买得到
Best counterfeit money can buy.
只是到底是如何让你觉得我们要带着这么多屎一样的东西？
And just how the hell do you think we're going to stow that much shit?
你担心了吗？伙计？我是说，你们的信心呢？
You worried, buddy? I mean, where is the faith?
你们看哈，我被降级了，现在我又要从头开始了？
What, I lost my stripes? Now I got to start from scratch?
没错，那些逼东西没用
Exactly, that shit's void.
没问题
No problem.
来吧，带你去
Come on, I'll show you.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
看起来不错，克里斯 你真他妈是个疯子
Looks good. Chris, you're a crazy fucker.
不错吧？ 60立方英尺
Not bad? Huh? Sixty cubic feet.
这他妈太大了吧 比60立方英尺还大
No fucking way. No, it's bigger than 60.
我草，是的 兄弟们 这个比60立方英尺还大
Ah, shit! Yeah, man, this is much bigger than 60.
有人来了
We got company.
快点，快点，快点
Quick, quick, quick!
嘿，克里斯，你在做什么？站住
Hey, what are you doing? Chris, stop!
安迪，呆在那里别出声
Andy, be quiet in there.
来吧，来吧！
Come on, come on!
你他妈的在那里干什么？
What the hell are you doing in here?
我需要一个铲子 我们注意到那下面好像有
I needed a scraper. We noticed some mold in the lower hull.
漂白济对它没有效果的，所以
The bleach wasn't cutting it, so...
你不能在这里东摸西摸的，快离开这里
Well, you shouldn't be dicking around in here. Get going.
我只是想帮你洗干净，长官
I was just trying to keep it clean for you, boss.
嘿，克里斯，克里斯
Hey, Chris! Chris!
把后面抬上来一点！加油 你能行的
Bring it right back up! Come on, you got it!
你能行的 加油！
You got it, come on!
我不行了
I can't do it.
日
God damn.
你要来试试吗？
Are you getting on?
不了
No.
你想我把你放到箱子里去吗？
Do you want me to put you back in the box?
这不好笑
That's not funny.
我会在箱子里憋死的
I could have suffocated in that box.
“我真的能”
"I really could have..."
放过那小孩吧
Leave the kid alone, man.
接下来你想怎样？
How are you going to pull this shit off?
他们提供300个左右的伪装箱
We're delivering 300 or so containers. Yeah.
我们拿500个或者更多 我们不准备进港
We're picking up 500 or more. We're not going to be in port that long.
因此，我们要去科沃瑞勒，见埃德温，完成这庄买卖
So we got to drive out to Chorrillo, see Edwin, load up the bills,
然后我们在最繁忙时候开车回到船上
and then drive back to the boat during rush hour.
时间有点紧，但是我们行的
It's going to be tight, but we're going to be good.
时间太紧了，我们得抓紧时间
It's going to be too tight. We're cutting it close.
可能时间还是不够
Might not have enough time.
我们想办法弄到更多时间
We'll buy more time.
可调螺旋桨
Controllable pitch propeller.
哦，明白了，螺旋桨
Oh, yeah. Pitch propeller.
你能掐断原油供应吗？
Can you drain the oil supply?
这样液压室就不能正常工作了
The hydraulic chamber won't work.
这才是重点，傻逼
That's the point, stupid ass.
听着
Look.
在锁被拖的时候，我们能做到这一点
We can do it while being towed through the locks.
这能为我们争取很多时间
It will buy us a couple of hours.
- 好吗？ -  我不知道
- Okay?       - I don't know.
我讨厌在船上工作
I hate when we fuck with the boat.
你说什么？
What?
我说，我讨厌在船上工作
I said, I hate when we fuck with the boat.
放轻松，大熊
Take it easy, big bear.
奥拉夫，去他妈的船
Olaf, fuck with the boat.
放轻松
Take it easy. Easy.
啥小啊？
What the fuck?
塔里克 那妈的会吃了你的
Tarik. That motherfucker will eat you.
好吧，出来吧
Okay, out you come.
- 你们想为我拿这些东西吗？ - 我们必须拿吗？
- Do you want to get any of these for me? - Do we have to?
好的，妈
Yes, Mom.
是吗？真好
Yeah? Okay.
你好？
Hello?
我能帮你什么吗？
Can I help you?
你真漂亮
You're pretty.
你不想玩玩吗？
Do you want to play?
好吧 再见，混蛋
Okay. Bye, asshole.
还钱，你欠我的
Pay the money just like you owe me.
你看娘的看什么看
What the fuck are you all looking at?
耶，你喜欢这样是吧？
Yeah, you like that?
把你他妈的手拿开
Get your fucking hands off me!
来吧，把刀子放下 把刀子放下
Come on, put the knife down. Put the knife down.
把刀子放下
Put the knife down.
放开我妈妈
Leave my mommy alone!
他妈的滚远点，别他妈的乱动
Get the fuck back over there! Sit your fucking ass down!
没关系的，我只是玩玩而已
It's okay, I'm just playing, now.
我只是玩玩
I'm just playing.
喂，不要哭嘛
Yeah, don't cry.
你以前见到过枪吗？你想要吗？
You seen a gun before? You want it?
下周我再来的时候就不仅仅是玩玩了
There ain't going to be no playing when I come back next week.
你可以给你老公说明这一点
You can tell your husband that.
你想要这个？滚出去
You want this? Get out!
搞什么？
What the fuck?
你们他妈的滚出我的房子！你们他妈的滚出我的房子！
Get the fuck out of my house! Get the fuck out of my house!
放下那东西
Put that thing down, man!
你觉得警查现在还不会来吗？
You don't think the police are going to be coming now?
快离开
Get the fuck out of here!
我不是想杀他的，是这个小混蛋自己撞上来的
I didn't mean to shoot at him. The little shit hit the gun.
你想让我回到农村里去吗？你个傻逼
You want to send me back to the farm, you stupid bitch?
噢，我的天
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
好的 小心 不是很多
All right, careful. Not too much.
我们不想让它堵塞 我明白了
I got it We don't want to jam it.
克里斯·法拉迪，到甲板上去
Chris Farraday, to the bridge.
在这里
Here.
他来了
He's on his way.
不要太多
Not too much.
好的
All right.
我没有接到你的电话
I wasn’t getting reception on your cell.
克里斯，这些家伙来家里了，他们还带着枪
Chris, these guys came to the house. They had guns.
杰西，你还好吧？孩子们都还好吧？
Jesus, are you okay? Are the boys okay?
嗯 我们都还好 我们吓坏了
Yeah, we're okay. We're freaked out.
我觉得其中一个就是蒂姆·布里格斯，凯尔的哥哥
I think one of them was Tim Briggs, Kyle's brother.
我没有打110，我不想警察在这里问东问西的
I didn't call the police, I don't want them here asking questions.
打给塞巴斯蒂安好吗？
Call Sebastian, okay?
嗯，好的 我会打的
Yeah, okay, I will.
好吧 我爱你 打给他
All right, I love you. Call him.
你老婆有麻烦了吗，法拉迪？
Trouble with the missus, Farraday?
你想让我跟她谈谈吗？
Do you want me to talk to her for you?
嘿，小盆友们，你们还好吧？你们今天吓着了吧？
Hey, guys, you okay? You had a scary day?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
你知道吗？你们为什么不
You know what? Why don't you guys
只是来我的地方
just come and stay at my place?
他们不会再回来了，只是为了让我自己安心
They're not going to be back, but just for my own peace of mind.
你觉得呢？
You think?
真的吗？好吧
Really? Okay.
慢慢的前进
Slow ahead.
我说了，慢慢的前进 减速到半速
I said, slow ahead! Reduce to half speed!
为什么我们减速了？
Why are we not slowing down?
油压下降了
Oil pressure's down.
好的 看好温度表
All right. Keep an eye on that temperature.
全速掉头
Full astern!
全速掉头，船长
Full astern, Captain.
- 嗯 船长？ - 全速掉头！
- Yeah, Captain? - Full astern!
我们要撞到石头上了
We're going to hit the fucking dock!
我正在尝试，不过我控制不了螺旋桨 他妈的卡住了
I'm trying, but I got no pitch control. The fucking prop is jammed!
你放太多油出来了！我并不是想让你撞翻这船
You drained too much oil out! I didn't want you to crash the boat!
什么？
What?
快点！我提升不了一点油压
Come on! I'm not getting any oil pressure!
我们入港
Let go the port anchor!
上帝啊，我草
Jesus, fucking...
我们他妈的快入港
Let go the fucking port anchor!
你松开刹车了吗？
Did you release the brake?
- 别挡道！ - 让开！
- Get out of the way! - Move!
打开右舷
Turn starboard!
太迟了！重撞港口！Luke！重撞港口！
It's too late! Hard to port, Luke! Hard to port!
我准备熄火
I'm going to have to kill the engine!
我草！
Fucking...
我们要撞上去了
We're going to hit!
他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on around here?
他们的发生什么事情了？
What the fuck happened?
螺旋桨卡住了
Propeller jam.
有人动过它
Someone tampered with it.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
肯定有人动过它
Someone tampered with it.
关于油的事情我很抱歉
Sorry about that oil thing.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
这会给我们争取更多时间
It will buy us a little more time.
嘿，迈克尔 快看 那就像一艘飞船
Hey, Michael, look. It's like a spaceship over here.
哇哦，塞巴斯蒂安，这里看起来真不错
Wow, Sebastian, it's amazing in here.
是吗？
Yeah? It's coming along, right?
我忘记你从装修之后就没来过这里了
I forgot you haven't been here since the renovation.
嘿，不要碰
Hey, don't touch that.
伙计们，你拿着这里
Fellas, you hang on to this.
好的 不错
Okay, that's good.
挺准的
Good aim.
嘿，都还好吧？
Hey, everything okay?
嗯，我们在塞巴斯蒂安家里
Yeah we're at Sebastian's.
孩子们都还好吧？
Are the boys okay?
嗯 你已经在巴拿马了吗？
Yeah. Are you in Panama already?
是的 保持联系
Yeah. Keep your phone on you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 我回头再打给你
I love you, too. I'll call you on my way back.
我们快到了
We're almost there.
嘿 哇
Hey! Whoa!
你养了很多猫嘛
You got a lot of pussy in here.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you, man.
- 都还好吧？ - 是的
- Everything good? - Yeah.
好的，你拿到钱了吧，那部车子？
Good, you got the cash, the van?
- 是的，是的 -  那就好
- Si, si.      - Cool.
什么，你不相信我？
What, you don't trust me?
噢，我当然相信你
Oh, I trust you.
这是很好的？
Esta bueno?
不，这是不他妈的很好
No, it's no fucking bueno.
安迪，在这里等着 丹尼，过来
Andy, wait here. Danny, come on.
嘿，怎么回事？你在做什么？
Hey, what is it? What are you doing?
我需要一些碘
I need some iodine.
墨水是OVI的，层次感很好
The ink is OVI, the layers are right,
但是那纸有种不同的感觉
but that paper felt different.
嘿，quepasa？发生了什么?
Hey, quepasa? What's going on?
你最好希望我是错的
You better hope I'm wrong.
你们他妈的傻逼在没有淀粉的纸张上打印
You fucking idiots didn't print this on starch-free paper.
对不起 这是我最好的了
I'm sorry, man. This is the best I have.
我没有时间听你狗屁
I don't have time for this.
我在电话里给你说过
I told you on the phone,
我需要的是跟你上次卖给我一样的货
I needed exactly what you sold me last time.
冈萨洛 冈萨洛在他仓库里藏有货
Gonzalo. Gonzalo has it at the warehouse.
冈萨洛？那个为杰西跪舔的傻逼？
Gonzalo? That little shithead who works for Jesus?
不是的，杰西已经不在了
No. There's no more Jesus.
冈萨洛现在就是老大
Gonzalo is running things now.
那你为什么不直接让我跟他做生意？
Why didn't you send me to him in the first place?
你他妈的玩我是吧？你他妈的玩我
Are you fucking playing games with me? Are you fucking playing...
我试过了！但他不希望任何人去那里
I tried! But he doesn't want anybody going there!
不要，不要，不要
No, no, no.
我们要去仓库 走！
We're going to the warehouse. Let's go.
不要不要不要
No, no, no, no, no.
克里斯
Chris.
嘿克里斯 听着，坐这车去，我很抱歉
Hey, Chris, man, look, take the van, man. I'm sorry.
快点，米奇！
Come on, Mikey!
这太阳真大
Man, the sun's really killing me.
那孩子子真状，是的 11号真是个状孩子
That kid is big. He is. Number 11 is a big kid.
等等，我要接个电话
Hold on, I got to take this.
好的
Okay.
嘿，怎么了？
Hey, man, what's up?
他没有货
He didn't have them.
好吧
All right.
好吧，我猜你会带些糖果回来
Well, I guess you're going to have to bring in some candy.
我不会带毒品的
I'm not bringing in drugs.
只要去见鲁本就好了
Just go and see Ruben.
我跟你说过，我不会运毒品的 好的，这没得选
I told you, I'm not bringing in drugs. Okay. It's not an option.
克里斯，我求你了
Chris, Chris, Chris, I'm begging you. Please.
克里斯？克里斯？
Chris? Yeah, Chris?
把他带到车上去
Put him in the fucking van.
你知道，如果你空手回来，
You know, you come back empty-handed,
安迪就死定了
Andy's going to get fucking hit,
而且你还得还老子那些钱
and you're still gonna have to come up with the goddamn money.
听着，我会想办法的，好吗？
Look, I'll figure it out, okay?
求你不要让布里格斯接近我的家人好吗？
Just keep Briggs away from my family, please.
嗯，当然没问题
Yeah, of course.
嘿，我工作上有些小问题，我得去解决一下
Hey, I got a little problem at work I got to take care of.
下次见，伙计
See you later, buddy.
拜拜 塞巴斯蒂安 都还好吗？
Bye, Sebastian. Everything okay?
嗯，都很好 你拿钥匙了吗？
Yeah, everything's fine. You got your key?
拿了
Yeah.
我给你说嘛，哥们 离冈萨洛远点
I'm telling you, man. Stay away from Gonzalo.
至人他当了老大以后，最近他都很疯狂
He's been acting crazy lately, since he became a boss.
离他远点
Stay away from him.
克里斯，我们应该听他的话的
Chris, we should have listened to him.
我们还有不到一个小时的时间回到船上 不会成功的
We got less than an hour to get back to the boat. It ain't going to work.
能行的
It will work.
我是说，你连冈萨洛的仓库在哪里你都不知道吧？
I mean, do you even know where Gonzalo's warehouse is?
我们现在在科沃瑞勒
We're in fucking Chorrillo right now.
我在找东西提醒我
I'm looking for something to remind me.
我们会找到它的
We're going to find it.
好的，好的 快看 就在这里！这里
Here we go. Here we go. Look, right here! Here!
- 摩丁 - 嗯 船长
- Mortin. - Yeah, Cap?
你看到他妈法拉迪了吗？
Where the hell is Farra-day?
我不知道，船长
I don't know, Cap.
我不知道我今天还要照看他 我没有得到命令
I didn't know I had to babysit him today. I didn't get the memo.
别他妈惹我，摩丁
Don't piss me off, Mortin.
你会在麦当劳得到狗屎面包
You'll be flipping shit-burgers at McDonald's
在你可以说"最低工资"之前
before you can say "minimum wage."
对不起 船长 对不起
I'm sorry, Cap. Sorry.
你去过凯特的家，也就是克里斯和他们孩子的家
That little visit you paid Kate, the kids, Chris' family?
他们也是我的家人
That's my family.
你离他们远点 听明白没？
You stay away from them. Are we clear?
你好，Sadie
Hi, Sadie.
你好
Hi.
你知道吗，如果你雇佣其他的走私犯替代安迪
You know, if you had hired a real smuggler instead of Andy,
我们的包裹会准时到达
our package would have come in when it was supposed to.
你知道的，我真的很抱歉
You know, I'm really sorry about that.
你知道现在这些逼事对我是什么感觉吗？
Do you know how fucked up things are for me right now?
我知道 他说他知道他在干什么
I know. He said he knew what he was doing.
我知道他是他小舅子
I didn't know he was his brother-in-law.
嘿，这条路比我预计的
Hey, man, this is way more high-risk
风险更高
than I originally anticipated.
现在我有妻子孩子
I got a wife now. I like my wife.
好吧，我也有妻子，好吗？
Yeah, I got a wife, too, okay?
别怕冈萨洛
And don't worry about Gonzalo.
我了解他，他只是他妈的一个皮条客 别担心
I know him, he's a little fucking punk. Don't worry about it.
噢是吗？我可听说一些传闻
Oh, yeah? I heard stories about this dude
把别人的头砍下来还有其他的
cutting people's heads off and shit.
我要找冈萨洛
I'm looking for Gonzalo.
安迪，你留在车里看包
Andy, stay in the van with the bag.
丹尼，没关系 的，我知道这哥们
Danny, it's all good. I know this guy, come on.
你有一个新消息
You have one new message.
嘿，傻逼头，我在看你妹妹的孩子玩足球
Hey, fuck head, I'm watching your sister's kid play soccer.
你没有回我电话
You don't call me back,
我准备在那空地里往他头里送颗子弹
I'm gonna walk out on that field and put a bullet in his head.
克里斯
Chris.
不要   别说了
Don't... Stop talking.
就像我说的一样，我要你
Like I said, I want you to take
带着钱到那个地址
the buy money and go to that address,
去找一个叫鲁本的人
and talk to a gentleman named Ruben.
如果你真的想再见到你的小外甥
If you ever want to see your little nephew again,
你拿着包回去，好吗？
you take the package and you bring it back, all right?
嘿，那是一只儿狼吗？
Hey, is that a wolf?
那不是他妈的狗
That ain't no fucking dog.
打扰一下，先生 你介意吗？
Av Excuse me, senor. Do you mind?
他在哪里？
Where is he?
我的老朋友法拉迪在哪里？
Where is my old friend Farraday?
把车开来
Bring the van around.
抱歉没有说声就来了
Sorry for showing up unannounced.
埃德温想跟我玩玩
Edwin was trying to play games with me.
我的老伙计杰西呢？
Where's my buddy Jesus?
我们把他喂狼了
We fed him to the wolves.
那是怎样啊？
What, literally?
我就是新的杰西，傻逼
I am the new Jesus, cabron.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
我也是
You, too.
你怎么看？
What do you think?
都是我的，傻逼
It's all mine, motherfucker.
这群混蛋谁敢说我没用啊？
All those assholes who thought I was shit?
我就送他们去见阎王
They're dead por culeros.
我们得拿下一卡车
We're taking down a truck.
要很大的一只，武装过的
It's a big one. An armored truck.
你想加入我们吗？
Do you want to join us? Huh?
你认真的？
Are you serious?
安迪？
Andy?
安迪！
Andy!
噢，我日
Oh, fuck.
安迪！
Andy!
他进攻…
He charges...
迈克尔不在家，我们是客人
Michael, not in the house. We're guests.
看这傻逼样
Look at young Daddy.
他射进了！
He shoots!
他得分了！
He scores!
去找你妈妈吧
Go find your mom.
你他妈想什么都准备好了 一点都不怕哈？
You ain't fucking around, huh? Looks like you're ready for anything.
你是想发动战争吗？
Are you going to war or something?
我给你说过，我们拿下了卡车 滚球鸡巴蛋吧你
I told you. We're taking down a truck. Fucking rock and roll.
开什么玩笑 你有这么多兄弟
No shit. You got all these guys.
那车里都他妈装得有什么东西啊？
What the fuck is in that truck, man?
你想知道吗？
You want to know?
也许你应该给你的兄弟们看看这是怎么完成的
Then maybe you should show these assholes how it's done.
不，你看哈
No, look...
我免费给你超级假钞
I'll give you the super notes for free.
好吧，还是谢谢你 不过我得去赶船，所以
Yeah, thanks anyway. But I got a boat to catch, so...
得了吧 别告诉我你不想念这些东西
Come on. Don't tell me you don't miss this shit.
我现在有两个孩子，你知道吗？我的古惑仔生涯已经结束了
I got two kids now, man, you know? My cowboy days are over.
快点，丹尼！
Come on, Danny!
钱不见了
The money's gone.
还有安迪
And Andy.
什么？
What?
你他妈的在说什么？
What the fuck are you talking about?
你来这里把我当傻逼耍哈？
You come in here and treat me like an asshole?
不是的 我怎么会呢
No, primo, I wouldn't do that, man.
我真他妈该一枪爆了你的头
I should fucking blow your brains out.
订单还有效吗？
Does that offer still stand?
我们跟了你，我的免费超级假钞还有吗？
We ride with you, I get the super notes for free?
是的，这里有些事情你可以帮我去做
Yeah, there's something you can do for us.
把他钱包拿过来
Grab their wallets.
把你钱包给他
Give him your wallet.
给我他们的身份证
Give me their IDs.
我们在这里停留的每一分钟都要罚款的，船长
We're being fined every minute longer we sit here, Captain.
我知道
Yep.
我们要拿到那个
We got to take that...
现在什么情况？
What's the status?
螺旋桨温度太高了，我们正在降温
Pitch propeller overheated. It needs oil. We're working on it.
给你十分钟搞定
You got 10 minutes!
是奥拉夫
It's Olaf.
克里斯，你有十分钟时间
Chris, you have got 10 minutes.
不够啊
That's not long enough.
让塔里克延迟启动
Have Tarik delay the loading.
尽量拖住他们好吧，越长越好，好吗？
Just stall them for as long as you can, okay?
快点到，我尽我全力
Get here. I'll do what I can.
看克里斯？这就是我最不想看到的
See, Chris? This is exactly what I didn't want to happen.
非常正确
Exactly.
我是说，我们本来就不该来这里的
I mean, what are we supposed to be doing here?
堵住卡车
Blocking the truck.
嗯 这样行得通
Right. That's awesome.
我们存在堵车
We're blocking the truck.
像人肉减速一样
Like human speed bumps.
告诉我老婆
Tell my wife that...
你他妈能闭嘴吗？
Will you shut the fuck up?
听着，我们能做好的，好吗？
Look, we're going to get through this, okay?
我不会告诉你老婆坏消息的！
I'm not telling your wife shit!
好的，准备好，他们来了
Okay, ready. They're coming.
系好你的安全带
Put your seatbelt on.
他们来了，我们走
He's coming down. Here we go.
我日
Fuck.
他会减速吗？
Is he going to slow down?
是的，他要减速了
Yeah, he's going to slow down.
你说他会减速的，他会减速的
You said he's going to slow down! He's gonna slow down.
他没有减速
He's not slowing down!
我草
Shit!
我日
Fuck!
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
噢，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
操！
Oh, fuck!
下来
Get down!
丹尼，你还好吗？
Danny, are you okay?
我需要你拿控制住DEF箱直到我说可以放手
I need you to hold containers D, E and F, until I say so.
我会给你100美元，好吗？
I'm going to pay you $100, yeah?
操！
Fuck!
你他妈在开玩笑吧？
You got to be fucking kidding me!
我草
Fuck!
趴下，克里斯
Get down, Chris!
我日
Fuck!
坚持住
Hold on.
我们在他妈的干鸟啊，兄弟？
What the fuck are we doing, dude?
等等，等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait!
快点
Come on!
我草
Shit!
我日 丹尼，快点，我们要走了
Shit! Danny, come on, we're going!
快点，丹尼，我们走，我日
Come on, Danny, let's go! Shit!
我日
Fuck!
现在怎样？
What now?
我日
Fuck!
安迪，克里斯哪去了？
Andy, where's Chris?
安迪！
Andy!
快点，我们走
Come on, we got to move!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我们得拿回我们的身份证
We got to get our IDs.
医院，我草
Oh, shit!
带我去他妈的医院吧
Take me to the fucking hospital.
噢，丹尼，我草 快来帮忙
Oh, shit. Danny, help.
来吧，躺下
Come on, lay down.
按住他，按住他
Hold him, hold him!
噢，我日 他死了吗？
Oh, shit! Is he dead?
他死了
He's dead!
如果他妈的死掉了，把他扔出车去吧
If he's fucking dead, throw him out the van.
等等，等等 拿回我们的身份证
Wait, wait! Get our IDs!
你拿到了？嗯
You got them? Yeah.
把他扔出去
Toss him out!
好的 小盆友们，把船启动起来吧
Okay, boys, let's warm her up.
你觉得我们还有多少时间 ？
How much time do you think we have?
没时间了
No time.
装好这些箱子，否则我们就只能抛弃他们了
Get those containers aboard or we're leaving without them.
克里斯，你们在他妈的哪里？船就要开了
Chris, where the fuck are you, man? The ship's leaving.
再拖一拖，我们就来
Just hold the ship, we're coming.
快点
Just get your ass over here!
好
All right.
船员都上船了吗？
Any crew member hasn't come aboard yet,
你搜一下他们
you make sure they get searched
在他们上船以前，明白吗？
before you let them on, you got me?
好吧 来吧 要开门了
All right, come on, it's going to open up.
我们能办到吗？
Are we going to make it?
哦耶，他在等着我们
Yeah, he's holding the container for us.
快点 冲冲冲
Come on. Go, go, go!
我来了，打开箱子
I'm coming. Open the container.
当你打开们的时间，带些东西来给我们清理一下
When you come to let us out, bring something to clean up a bit of a mess.
别忘了封条 好吧
Don't forget the seals! Okay.
我草
Shit.
好，我们走
Yeah, yeah. Here we go.
他妈的别挡路
Get the fuck out of the way!
快点 快进去
Come on, get your ass in here!
我草，我草
Fuck! Fuck!
我日
Shit!
等等，停一下
Wait, stop!
快点
Come on!
他妈的门是开着的
The fucking doors are open!
噢，我日
Oh, fuck!
我能搞定它
I got it.
噢 ，我日
Oh, fuck!
等等，怎么了？
Hold up. What's the rush?
快点
Come on.
我只是忘了一些吃的，你懂的
I just left some food on, you know? Come on, Jack.
船长说过要检查每一个下船的船员
Captain has got us searching everybody that got off.
嘿，你准备去哪？
Hey, where are you going?
我只是藏了些牛肉
I just stowed some decent beef.
哦，老天
Ooh! Thank God.
你昨晚做的菜就像屎一样
That shit you made last night was like chewing ass.
呵呵，你应该了解的
Yeah, you would know.
我草你妈，塔里克
Fuck you, Tarik.
快点
Come on.
- 你带了清洁的东西了吗？ - 嗯
- You got the cleaning stuff? - Yeah.
- 你拿了封条了吗？ - 嗯
- You got the seals? - Yeah.
好吧 我们来迟了，他们肯定会来检查的
All right, we got on late They're definitely going to check this.
我呢个草
Holy shit!
我们走，宝贝
Let's go, baby.
干得好
Will do.
船长，是海关和边防
Customs and Border Protection, Captain.
他们想让我们去检查一下最后上来的箱子
They want us to take a look at some containers that were loaded late.
好的 去吧
All right, let's go.
呼叫第二线路
Call in the Second.
我们走，丹尼  我们走
Let's go, Danny. Let's go.
我们要找的是哪个
Where are we looking, Chief?
那上面的箱子，船长
The container right up here, Captain.
812504.
８１２…
812...
对不起，船长
Sorry, Captain.
下一个
Next.
我日
Oh, shit.
我要去检查一下暧气管，等等，等等
I'm gonna check the heating coils... Wait, wait!
我需要几分钟时间
...I'm gonna need a couple of minutes.
快点，我们走
Come on, let's go.
2727.
812729.
我日 老鼠
Oh! Shit, rats!
快关上！
Shut it!
小心手
Watch your hand.
我们下水道漏了，打给布罗迪好吗？
We got a sewage leak. Call Brody, all right?
好的，我们走
All right, let's go.
上面还有两个集装箱
We got two more containers up here.
南森-812552
Nathan-812552,
812553.
就是这个，打开它
That's it, open it.
525524.
这就是最向上船的箱子
That's the last container that was boarded.
继续
Goon.
有什么发现吗？
Anything?
没有，长官，闻起来像刚被清洗过一样
No, sir. Smells like it was just cleaned.
好吧 封上
All right, seal it up.
等我们到家的时候，海关会拆了它的
Customs will take it apart when we get back home.
我得告诉你
I need to tell you...
你他妈脑子有毛病吗？
Are you out of your fucking mind?
你他妈疯了吗？
Are you fucking crazy?
钱去哪了，钱在哪？
Where's the money? Where is it?
钱不见了，我很需要这笔钱
It's gone! I had to use it.
什么？钱哪？
It's what? Where's the money?
你想干什么？
What are you trying to...
你刚才对我说神马？
What did you just say to me?
我真的很需要这笔钱
I had to use it.
什么？
You what?
我需要钱！
I had to use it.
钱在天花板上
It's in the ceiling.
操，狗日的
No, you fucking...
你他妈脑残啊？
How fucking stupid are you?
我他妈冒着失去自由的危险来帮你
I came out here to help you, to risk my fucking freedom
为了这个还不顾有我的妻子和孩子的安危
and my wife and my children for this?
妈的
Motherfucker.
我到底该怎么处理？
What the fuck am I supposed to do with all that?
你必须给老子装傻
You got to be the dumbest motherfucker...
我说他要杀了迈克尔
He said he was going to kill Michael.
神马？
What?
你了新一条消息
You have one saved message.
嗨，小混蛋，我看到你姐姐的孩子在足球
Hey, fuck head, I'm watching your sister's kid play soccer.
你不用打给我了
You don't call me back,
老子要马上去给他脑袋上一枪
I'm gonna walk out on that field and put a bullet in his head.
去拿包
Get the bag.
你还好吧？
Are you all right? Yeah.
你怎么样，还好吧？
You all right? You all right?
嗯，我没事
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
对不起，冷静点，冷静点
I'm sorry. Calm down, calm down.
嗨
Hey.
一切都还好吗？孩子们没事吧？
Everything okay? Boys all right?
嗯，他们正在睡觉呢
Yeah, they're sleeping.
出什么事了，都还好吗，安迪没事吧？
What's up? Is everything okay? Is Andy okay?
嗯 不用担心 塞巴斯蒂安在哪儿吗？
Yeah. Don't worry about it. Is Sebastian there?
嗯，他在 要不要我叫他过来？
Yeah, he is. Do you want me to get him for you?
不用了
No, no.
对，没事 回去睡觉吧
No, it's okay. Go back to sleep.
我明天早上叫你
I'll call you in the morning.
嗯 我爱你
Okay. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
克里斯？
Chris?
克里斯，我刚刚一直在叫你，出什么事了？
Chris, I've been trying to call you. What's going on?
安迪收拾点东西
Andy picked something up.
真的？我以为不用的，
Really? I thought we weren't doing that.
我没得选择
I didn't have a choice.
太好了 安迪主动了一点哈
Thank God for Andy taking the initiative, though, huh?
不幸的是 我没带过来
Too bad I'm not bringing it in.
其实我想把它丢到海里
I'm thinking of dumping it in the sea, actually.
你为什么要那么做呢？
Why would you do that?
那样我们都会解脱的
Then we would all be fucked!
自信点，没问题的
Take it on faith.
我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
出什么事了吗？
Is something wrong?
我告诉过你一有新消息就给你电话
I told you I would call you with an update.
你还几天时间
You've got a few more days left
在老子把你脑袋拧下来塞你屁眼上之前
before I cut your head off and stick it up your ass.
那你还问我“出什么事了”吗？
And you're asking me, "Is there anything wrong?"
好吧，我有些东西要进来
Well, I got something coming in.
听起来你不是很确定
You don't sound so sure.
我确定 它进来了
I'm sure. It's coming in.
这样可不好，阿布尼
Flying solo ain't for sidekicks, Abney.
我他妈警告过你的
I fucking warned you.
当你第一次来找我帮忙的时候
When you first came to me for help
为了你那小生意
in keeping your little business afloat,
我他妈警告过你的
I fucking warned you.
你得了解你自己的极限
I said, "You've got to know your limitations."
别超过你他妈的极限了
"Don't live beyond your fucking means!"
我平常都不干这些2B事情的
I don't normally do this fucking shit.
告诉你如果不付钱会是什么样的后果
Telling you what's going to happen when you don't pay.
什么是他妈的重点？你知道规则的，对吗？
What's the fucking point? You know the rules, right?
嗯
Right.
你自求多福，阿布尼
You take care, Abney.
杰克
Jack, neat.
有些人没有戒掉酒哦
Somebody's off the wagon.
我想你去看看凯特
I want you to go see Kate.
兄弟，我以为她也是你的家人
Man, I thought she was your family.
你知道的，如果你想草他老婆，你去草就是了
You know, if you want to fuck his wife, you fuck his wife.
但是，别浪费老子的时间在这里扮英雄
But don't waste my time so you can play hero.
克里斯在那里搞砸了
Chris is falling apart out there.
他要丢掉那批货了
He's going to dump the package.
别碰她，只要引她注意就好了
Don't touch her. Just get her attention.
好吧
All right.
Yeah.
哇噻
Oh, man.
你觉得这样有用吗？
Do you think it's going to work?
肯定有用的，你觉得是这样？
It's going to work. You think so?
你学校念的科学吗？塔里克
Did you take science in school, Tarik?
嗯
Yeah.
那你应该知道盐在水里会溶解吧，傻逼
Then you should know salt dissolves in water, bitch.
你很快就要走吗？
Are you leaving soon?
嗯，塞巴斯蒂安马上就把孩子送来
Yeah, Sebastian is dropping the boys off.
我们要回家了
We're going home.
噢，是哦，克里斯要回来了
Oh, that's right. Chris is coming home.
嗯
Yeah.
这就是你早上一直在笑的原因吧？
So, you'll be all smiles in the morning?
我希望如此
I hope so.
你先走吧，我来弄这些
You get out of here, I got it.
晚安
Good night.
晚安 晚安，宝贝
Good night. Good night, baby.
我会锁好门的
I'll lock the door.
谢谢
Thanks.
哦，我的天呀！
Oh. My God!
你他妈的离我远点！
Get the fuck away from me!
我的朋友将来这里，他会踢你的
My friend will be here, he'll kick your...
我要完全他妈的明确一下
I'm going to be perfectly fucking clear.
你打电话给你老公，叫他不要将它扔进水中！
You call your husband and you tell him not to dump it in the water!
你告诉他，你、迈克尔和Eddie的生死取决于他
You tell him that you, Michael and Eddie are all depending on him.
懂了吗？
Do you understand me?
知道我的意思了吗？
放开我的孩子！
Stay away from my kids!
他有枪！
He's got a gun!
喔！你在干什么？
Whoa! What are you doing?
嘿
Hey.
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
宝贝，我要你和我一起进卡车
Honey, I want you to get in the truck with me.
孩子们在里面，好不？
The kids are inside, all right?
你闻起来就像个酒桶
You smell like alcohol.
是的，我喝了点酒
Yeah, I had a drink.
你正在醉酒驾车？你他妈的开玩笑吧？
You're driving my kids around drunk? Are you fucking kidding me?
放松，他和你说了什么？
Relax. What did he say to you?
来吧，出来吧 我们将去我的车，走吧
Come on, get out. We're going in my car. Let's go.
凯特！孩子们，回我的车
Kate! Guys, get back in the car.
凯特，你在干什么？
Kate, what are you doing?
凯特！凯特！进我的卡车
Kate! Kate! Get in the truck.
他妈的！
Fuck.
他知道孩子们的名字
He knew the kids' names.
别挂，信号不好，好不？我出去一下
Hold on, you're breaking up, okay? Let me go outside.
哦，他妈的
Oh, fuck.
这里的手机服务很烂，别挂，我正在跑出去
Cell service sucks here on the river. Hold on, I'm going outside.
在吗？他叫我告诉你
Hello? He told me to tell you...
不，别挂 我听不清
No, hold on. I can't hear you.
他叫我告诉你不要把它扔进
He told me to tell you not to dump it in...
他叫我告诉你不要把它扔了
He told me to tell you not to dump it.
谁？
Who did?
谁？那个来我房子的混蛋！
Who? The asshole who came to the house!
谁他妈的告诉他？
Who the fuck told him?
什么？
What?
孩子们都没事吧？
Are the boys okay?
他们在这里，我们正在珍妮家
They're here. We're at Jeanie's.
凯特？在吗？
Kate? Hello?
克里斯，请回家
Chris, please come home.
克里斯？
Chris?
嘿，咋么样？
Hey, how did it go?
我们登上了前窗
We boarded up the front window.
警察做了一份报告，他们正在寻找这个家伙
The cops took a report. They're looking for the guy.
好吧
All right.
他们想和你谈话
They want to talk to you.
好的，我会在早上去的
Yeah. I'm going to go by in the morning.
他们想和你现在谈一下
They want to talk to you now.
但是我们没有货 我们只有去塞巴斯蒂安那去得到我们的货
But we have no stuff. I've got to go to Sebastian's to get our stuff.
你介意我看一下孩子们吗？
Would you mind watching the boys for a second?
瞧你的前额
Look at your forehead.
你确定不需要送你去医院？
Are you sure you don't need me to take you to the hospital?
不用，这只是   它比实际看起来更糟糕
No, it's just... It looks worse than it is.
它只是个伤口 就像一个挫伤，你知道吗？
It just hurts. Like a bruise, you know?
我觉得我现在不得不离开，你知道我的意思？
I think I should go now before I can't. You know what I mean?
我过一会来看你
I'll see you in a little bit.
拜拜，妈妈，我爱你
Goodbye, Mom. I love you.
做好孩子
Be good boys.
塞巴斯蒂安？
Sebastian?
你告诉布里格斯我已经决定扔了它？
Did you tell Briggs I was going to dump it?
不，我没有告诉任何人
No. I didn't tell nobody.
不要骗我
Don't lie to me.
克里斯，我没有必要他妈的骗你，我没有说啊，他妈的
Chris, I'm not fucking lying to you. I didn't say shit.
你从哪里得到这些药品？
Where did you get the drugs?
从一个叫鲁本的家伙
From a guy called Ruben.
塞巴斯蒂安？
Sebastian?
嘿
Hey.
嗨，我只是拿我的行李
Hi. I'm just getting our stuff.
你饿了吗？我给你做些吃的？
Are you hungry? Let me make you some food.
不，不用了
No, I can't.
船没有来，我将会孩子那边去
The boat's not coming in. I got to get back to the boys.
克里斯今晚将回来
Chris will be back tonight.
不，他没有 他今晚不回家
No, he's not. He's not coming home tonight.
我的意思是，船没有来，就像，我不知道，明天会不会
I mean, the boat's not coming in for, like, I don't know, tomorrow.
克里斯叫我来照顾你
Chris told me that I had to take care of you,
我就要照顾好你
so I'm going to take care of you.
塞巴斯蒂安，你没有听我说吗？对我们都好，好不？
Sebastian, are you not hearing me? We'll be fine, okay?
是的，对我们都好
Yeah, we're fine.
好了，就这样，好
Okay, good. All right. Good.
给我个拥抱
Give me a hug.
好，好
Okay. Okay.
这是个大日子
It's been such a big day.
你他妈的在做什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
没有 我没有做任何事
Nothing. I'm not doing anything.
我试着给我的朋友一个他妈的吻 你有什么问题吗？
I'm trying to give my friend a fucking kiss. What's your problem?
你遇到什么问题了？凯特，说一下
What's your problem? Kate, come on.
看，我的意思是，你曾经看到这个吗？
Look, I mean, did you even see this?
停下来
Stop it.
凯特
Kate.
我们认识多久了？
How long have we known each other?
你知道什么？让你的手放开我！
You know what? Get your hands off me!
凯特？凯特！
Kate? Kate!
让我单独呆一会！
Leave me the fuck alone!
凯特！
Kate!
凯特
感谢上帝，凯特
Jesus Christ. Kate!
我只是想和你谈谈
I'm trying to have a conversation with you,
你却表现的像个该死的小孩
and you're acting like a fucking child.
那好，你为什么不从这门出去
Okay. Good. Why don't you just walk away from the door,
让我们一起离开这儿
and let me get out of here.
一个忘恩负义的小孩，该死的讨厌鬼，就不会感激人吗
An ungrateful child. A little fucking brat, who's not grateful for...
你想和克里斯说我是个臭婊子吗？
Do you want to talk to Chris about what a fucking bitch I am?
我现在马上去给他打个该死的电话
I'm going to fucking call him on the phone right now!
不要给他打电话
Don't call Chris.
亲爱的，我爱你，请开门
Sweetheart, I love you, but open the door.
我正在和克里斯通话
I'm calling Chris!
现在别惹他
Don't mess with his head now!
该死的你怎么不告诉他？
Why don't you fucking tell him?
该死
Shit!
亲爱的，对不起，你还好吗？
Honey, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
凯特？
Kate?
凯特，这一点儿也不好笑，不要再转悠了
Kate, it's not funny. Stop fucking around.
操
Fuck.
你会没事的
You're going to be okay. You're going to be okay.
该死
Shit.
凯特？
Kate?
凯特！
Kate! Kate!
嗨
Hey.
我知道你做了什么
I know what you did.
我知道布里格斯为你工作
I know Briggs works for you.
该死的离我家远点，要不然我就杀了你
You stay the fuck away from my family, or I'm going to kill you.
你听见了吗？
You hear me?
只需要把包裹带来，一切都会好的
Just bring in the package . Everything's going to be fine.
我不会带来的
I'm not bringing in shit.
你永远也不会见到那个该死的包裹
You'll never see that fucking package.
你知道的，我什么都不清楚
You know, I didn't know about...
我不相信你，你在玩我
I can't believe you. You fucking played me
我没有玩你
I'm not playing you.
我来了，向你走过来
I'm coming. I'm coming for you.
好的
Okay.
坎普船长
Captain Camp.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian.
阿布尼，你想要什么？
What do you want, Abney?
克里斯·法拉迪跑了
Chris Farraday is running shit.
好的
Okay.
他正要去把包裹给倒掉
He's going to dump the package.
如果你确信他没有，我会把他的那份给你
If you make sure he doesn't, I will give you his share.
天啊，阿布尼 你就是个冷血性急的混蛋
Jesus, Abney. You are one cold rat bastard.
完全正确
All right.
但是如果法拉迪不放弃
But if Farraday don't give it up,
我将通知警方，你的东西会被查获
I'm going to call in the dogs, and your package is getting seized.
不，他会告诉你在哪的，他才不蹲班房
No, he'll tell you where it is. He won't risk doing time.
下次你就要在我船上屙大了
Next time you want to run shit on my ship,
你搞定它然后跟其他人一样付票费
you do it right and pay a fare like everybody else.
它在哪？
Where is it? Where's what?
你在干着什么事，我知道你
You're running something. I know you're running something.
我什么也没做，船长
I'm not running anything, Captain.
你想那样来解决？大副
You want to play that way? Check.
这是你的一个机会
This is your one chance.
你想放弃了，还是想让我叫CBP过来（美国海关与边防局）
You give it up now, or you want me to call CBP?
我什么也没做
I'm not running anything.
你老婆叫我带个毛的巴拿马狗回家
Your wife asked me to bring some Panamanian dog shit home
喂上面或者她下面
for her to eat and rub in her fucking cunt...
操，你个垃圾 我没时间乱吹
Fuck you, you piece of shit. But I didn't have time.
你个婊子养的！这样子就是你想要的？
You dumb-ass motherfucker! This is how you want it?
对，我就是想这样
Yeah, this is how I want it.
你跟你爸一样下地狱吧
You want to go down just like your dumb-ass daddy,
你个SB爱尔兰人
you piece of shit mick?
操
Fuck this.
是你搞成这样的，操尼玛
You made it now, motherfucker.
恩？
Right?
不管是什么，CBP（美国海关与边防局）会搞清楚的
Whatever it is, CBP is going to find it.
恩他在吃自助餐
Yeah, he's in the cafeteria.
你ok了
You're clear.
来啊 快点
Come on, come on.
操，把电话捡起来，哥们
Shit! Pick up the phone, buddy.
美国海关和边境保护局，新奥尔良港
Customs and Border Protection, Port of New Orleans.
是雷蒙德，在2号线
It's Redmond, line two.
雷蒙德
Redmond.
嗨，约翰，我玩的可嗨了
Yeah, John, I've got a good tip.
有人在我船上闹事
Somebody's making a run on my ship.
真的假的？
Really?
好了，小伙子们姑娘们，听着
All right, listen up, guys and gals,
20分钟后我要一支封锁的队伍
I want an interdiction team ready for deployment in 20 minutes.
走起
Let's go.
104号，收到请回答，三分钟后再联络
Flight 104, copy that. Three minutes to contact.
各就各位，准备战斗
Ready. Standing by.
TMD！
Holy shit!
好吧，还是撑了好一会儿
Well, it was good while it lasted.
哪个混蛋把装甲兵召唤过来的？
Who the fuck called the cavalry in?
请检查！
Inspection, please!
全员都有！
All crew. Everybody.
谁在哪？
Who's in here?
欢迎上船
Welcome aboard.
好了，先生们，请坐下
All right, gentlemen, sit down.
发生了什么JB事？
What the fuck is going on?
拉瑞，查看下天花板
Larry, check the ceiling.
放松，别紧张！
Take it down.
哇，快看这个
Wow! Look at this.
这儿什么也没有
There's nothing in there.
什么都没有？
There's nothing in there?
妈的！
Shit!
那就足够了
That's enough.
一个防水布
A tarp.
一个没有任何东西在里面的工具箱
Tool box with nothing in it.
你说你认为它闻上去很滑稽，是吗？
You said you thought it smelled funny, right?
是的，队长
Yes, Captain.
或许它刚被清扫过 应该就是这样
Maybe it's just been cleaned. That's about it.
有可能是被什么东西盖住了吗？
Could be covering up something, maybe?
的确有可能
Could be.
看着点
Watch your step.
仅仅把干净点的毛毯放进卡车就行了
Just put the carpet cleaner in the trunk.
你明白吗？
You got it?
放在那里就好了
Just put it right there, that's fine.
擦
Fuck.
Oh，妈的
Oh, shit.
蓬车在D-7
The van in D-7.
什么意思？
What about it?
我们正在把它拆散
We're taking it apart now.
但是你可以解决我们的麻烦，然后给我们说里面有什么
But you can just save us the trouble, and tell us what's in it.
我很希望能帮到你
I would love to help you,
但是我完全不知道你在说些什么
but I don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
你认为我们很笨？
Do you think we're stupid?
谁是吉布·拉科瓦斯基？
And who is Jib Lakowski?
他就在这，他就是运送车的那个人
It says right there, he's the guy shipping the van,
所以你或许应该去找他谈谈
so maybe you should talk to him.
他在2004年就死了
He died in 2004.
那么我猜他肯定用不着这辆车了，是吧？
Then I guess he's not going to need the van. Huh?
怎么了，“胡迪尼”？
What's up, Houdini?
你给我带了什么东西？
You got something for me?
你在说些什么？
What are you talking about?
算了吧，给他吧
Come on, man. Just give it to him.
你他妈在说什么？
What the fuck are you talking about?
算了吧，伙计
Come on, man!
好吧，我倒是不这样认为 给安迪说再见吧
Yeah, I didn't think so. Say goodbye to Andy.
闭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
别冲我吼！
Don't fuck me, man!
你都在干些什么？
What are you doing?
克里斯
Chris!
安迪，跑！
Run, Andy!
妈的，布里格斯
Fuck, Briggs.
快扣动扳机
Pull the fucking trigger!
如果我死了你不会得到你想要的药
You don't get your dope if I'm dead.
这边
Here.
他就在这里啊
This is it right here.
这里？
Right here?
是的
Yeah.
什么，你让你奶奶卖可卡因？
What, you got your grandma selling cocaine?
那是我朋友的地盘
It's my friend's place.
你最好别胡闹
You better not be messing around,
不然我给你一脚
I'll put a bullet in your face.
好吧，别紧张，那没什么
All right, take it easy. Come on.
- 这是你朋友的家？  - 安静点
- Is your friend home?   - Quiet.
相信我，你绝对不想把这个混蛋吵醒的
Trust me, you don't want to wake this fucker up.
你，就呆在那别动
One, state your position, please.
211，请回答
211, responding.
我们有个家庭安保系统触发装置在452 King Drive
We have a home security alarm triggered at 452 King Drive.
嘿，你的朋友很有钱啊
Hey, you got some rich friends, man.
算了吧
Come on.
关上门
Shut that door.
世界级的走私就在那儿啊
That's some world-class smuggling right there, man.
Yeah！
Yeah!
我们拿到它了
We got it now, man.
检查一下
Check this out.
没必要吧
This is the shit, man.
检查一下！
Check this out.
好的
Yeah.
这儿有一些真正的booger-sugar
Oh, that's some real booger-sugar right there.
哼哼，是的
Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
很棒吗？
It's good?
是的，是的
Yeah, yeah.
太好了 我先去撒个尿
Great. I'm going to take a piss,
我要拿着它直到我下船
I've been holding it since I got off the boat.
好吧，你拿着吧
All right, you do that.
他不想出来
It doesn't want to come out, man.
他们把它弄得太难对付了
They make it stubborn...
你他妈是谁？
Who the hell are you?
你他妈在我房子里干什么？
What the fuck are you doing in my goddamn house?
躺回床上去吧，老头
Go back to bed, old man.
妈的，五点了！
Shit, it's Five-O!
滚出去，把这个包上
Get the fuck out! Pack that shit up, man.
妈的
Dumb shit.
珍妮，凯特在哪吗？她不接电话
Jeanie, is Kate there? She's not picking up her phone.
男孩们都和你在一起吗？
Are the boys with you?
是的，男孩们都在这 她离开了一会儿
Yeah, the boys are here. She left a while ago.
说她要去塞巴斯蒂安拿他们的东西
Said she was going to Sebastian's to get their stuff.
听着，如果她打电话给你，告诉她马上给我打电话
Listen, if she calls you, tell her to call me right away.
真他妈搞笑
Absolutely fucking ridiculous.
我还从没有看见过这种蠢蛋
I've never seen these idiots before in my life.
在那的那个蠢货流的血滴满了我的椅子
That one dumbs hit right there is bleeding all over my couch,
并且他们还在切他们的药
and they're cutting up their drugs.
凯特？
Kate?
凯特！
Kate!
塞巴斯蒂安！
Sebastian!
你们先把这些混凝土倒到南边的角落里
I want you guys to pour the cement on the south corner first.
我们可以先从南边开始么？
Can we start on the south corner first?
- 我们从另一边开始  - 不，不行
- We're set up for the other side. - No, we can't.
快点从南边的角落开始
South corner first hurry the hell up.
你们已经耽搁的时间已经够长了！
You guys have milked this fucking job long enough!
接着！
Hold it!
我们先从南边开始 把它弄到那边去
We're pouring over on the south corner. Take it over there.
这到底是怎么回事？我以为我们是从另外一边开始
What the hell's going on here? I thought we were doing the other side.
你为什么要把水泥车弄到那边去？
Why are you moving the cement truck?
你会把这些该死的车子堵在一块儿
You're blocking the fucking trucks.
是你派人到我家去的？
You send guys to my house?
哼？我们一家人都那么相信你
Huh? I trusted you with my wife and my kids.
我他妈把你当兄弟一样
And I fucking loved you like a brother.
凯特在哪里？
Where is Kate?
凯特到底在哪儿？
Where the fuck is Kate?
最后再问你一次 凯特在哪儿？
One more fucking time. Where's Kate?
她不见了
She's gone.
你还好吧，赛博？
Are you okay, Seb?
这是谁的手机？
Whose phone is this?
谁把手机落在这儿了？
Who left their phone here?
把那鬼东西关掉，快点！
Turn that fucking thing off, now!
克里斯？
Chris?
噢 天呐！
Oh. My God!
快把那鬼东西停下来！
Turn that fucking thing off!
快叫救护车！
Call an ambulance!
噢，操
Oh, fuck.
快叫救护车！！
Call an ambulance!
快叫该死的救护车，快点！
Call a fucking ambulance, now!
对，快派救护车过来
Yeah, I need an ambulance...
噢，shit
Oh, shit.
在西海岸载重汽车公司 是的，快点！
...at West Bank Trucking Company. Yeah, right away.
你确定就是这儿吗？
Are you sure this is the right place?
对
Yeah.
克里斯放弃时给力我这些坐标
These are the coordinates Chris gave me when he dropped it.
我们肯定在正确的地点
We're definitely in the right place.
克里斯
Chris.
对不起 真的对不起
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我拿那 这给你
I got that. And you got one.
你作弊 这是我的
You cheated. It's mine.
噢!
Oh!
是的!
Yeah!
噢，兄弟，我相信不敢相信
Oh, man! I can't believe it.
大海里全是钱
A sea full of money!
我们要下去
We got to get in.
从这儿下去，哈哈
Get it in here. Yeah.
拉过来，小心点 那里有点滑
Pull it in. Be careful, it's slippery right there.
哇
Whoa!
你还好吧？
Are you all right?
嗯 还好
Yeah, I'm all right.
巴德？
Bud?
我已经卖了它
And I have sold it.
4500，106号 下一个
4,500, number 106. Next one.
开始第122号 出价300美元起
Call lot number 122. Come bid 300.
高于300，我出价400
A high of 300, I have to get 400.
到400了，出价500了 有出550吗？
Got 400, got a $500 bid. Five-and-a-half?
500到650
Five to six-and-a-half.
我出700，到750了
I'm going to seven, going to seven-and-a-half.
有人出800吗？800吗？
Can I have an $800 bid? Get an 800?
我卖了它
And I have sold it.
第77号以750成交 谢谢你 下一个
Seven-and-a-half to number 77. Thank you, sir. Next one.
我以2.5倍买你手里的货
I'll take it off your hands for 2.5.
低于3倍我就不卖
I'm not taking any less than three.
好吧，就3倍
Okay, three.
来吧
Come on.
所以你拿下了巴拿马的货？
So you were down in Panama, were you?
嗯
Yeah.
你有没有听说过杰克逊·波洛克（美国抽象表现主义的代表人物）的名画？
Did you hear about that famous painting by Jackson Pollock?
它在巴拿马被偷了
It got ripped off in Panama.
算了吧你，这消息到处都有
Come on, it's been all over the news.
不 不知道
No. No idea.
那东西值多少钱？
What's that thing worth, anyway?
大概1亿4千万美元
About 140 million.
那就是说，黑市价格是两千万？
What's that, 20 on the black market?
至少
At least.
我是不是做错生意了？
I'm in the wrong business, huh?
进来，进来
Get in, get in.
快点！
Hurry LIP!
两千万
Twenty.
两千万！两千万！
Twenty! It's twenty!
两千万
Twenty million.
好！
Yes!